"dota"
{
"TitleText"	"{s:TitleTextVar}"
"[english]TitleText"	"{s:TitleTextVar}"
"BodyText"	"{s:BodyTextVar}"
"[english]BodyText"	"{s:BodyTextVar}"
"ProgressText"	"{s:ProgressTextVar}"
"[english]ProgressText"	"{s:ProgressTextVar}"
"EndScreenClose"	"退出"
"[english]EndScreenClose"	"EXIT"
"InfoScreenClose"	"继续"
"[english]InfoScreenClose"	"CONTINUE"
"ag_alert_InvulnerabilityTitle"	"战斗已暂停"
"[english]ag_alert_InvulnerabilityTitle"	"Combat Paused"
"ag_info_PreGamePrepTitle"	"筹备战斗：制胜的关键"
"[english]ag_info_PreGamePrepTitle"	"Planning: The Key to Victory"
"ag_info_PreGamePrepBody"	"在Dota中，战前的筹备与自身的技术同样重要。一流的团队会挑选可以相互配合的英雄，受到攻击可以来回援护，还能共同达成目标。筹备的技巧会随着参与比赛的增多逐渐得到积累。现在，我们先专注于做好一个定位。"
"[english]ag_info_PreGamePrepBody"	"In Dota, planning is just as important as skill. The best teams choose heroes which complement each other, support each other when under attack, and try to take objectives together. These are things you will learn with time. For now, we'll focus on doing well in one role."
"ag_info_YourRoleTitle"	"你的定位：积累力量，然后消灭敌人"
"[english]ag_info_YourRoleTitle"	"Your Role: Gather Power, then Destroy the Enemy"
"ag_info_YourRoleBody"	"在这场比赛中，你只要专心增强自己在游戏中后期的力量。\n\n有了相当的等级和装备后，你就会在战斗中所向披靡，具备快速摧毁防御塔的能力。\n\n电脑将控制你的队友，在你周围保证你不受打扰。"
"[english]ag_info_YourRoleBody"	"In this match you will focus on building toward Mid to Late Game power.\n\nWith a few levels and items you will be powerful in fights and able to destroy Towers quickly.\n\nThe bots which control your teammates will try to work around what you do."
"ag_info_GamePlanTitle"	"比赛流程"
"[english]ag_info_GamePlanTitle"	"Game Plan"
"ag_info_GamePlanBody"	"1）购买初始物品，准备作战\n2）在自己的分路上保证生存的同时获取金钱和经验\n3）完成对小兵的正补，获取额外的金钱\n4）购买前期装备，强化英雄\n5）与队友摧毁敌方防御塔\n6）摧毁敌方兵营\n7）摧毁敌方遗迹，赢得比赛"
"[english]ag_info_GamePlanBody"	"1) Prepare by purchasing your Starting Items\n2) Survive in your lane to earn Gold and Experience\n3) Strike the Last Hit on creeps to earn additional gold\n4) Buy Early Game Items to strengthen your hero\n5) Destroy enemy Towers with teammates\n6) Destroy the enemy Barracks\n7) Destroy the enemy Ancient to win the match"
"ag_objective_LunaUnlockAbilityTitle"	"学习技能"
"[english]ag_objective_LunaUnlockAbilityTitle"	"Learn Ability"
"ag_objective_LunaUnlockAbilityBody"	"点击“学习技能”按钮并学习技能“月之祝福”。"
"[english]ag_objective_LunaUnlockAbilityBody"	"Press the \"Level Up\" button and learn the Lunar Blessing ability."
"ag_objective_SvenUnlockAbilityTitle"	"学习技能"
"[english]ag_objective_SvenUnlockAbilityTitle"	"Learn Ability"
"ag_objective_SvenUnlockAbilityBody"	"点击“学习技能”按钮并学习技能“风暴之拳”。"
"[english]ag_objective_SvenUnlockAbilityBody"	"Press the \"Level Up\" button and learn the Storm Hammer ability."
"ag_objective_LinaUnlockAbilityTitle"	"学习技能"
"[english]ag_objective_LinaUnlockAbilityTitle"	"Learn Ability"
"ag_objective_LinaUnlockAbilityBody"	"点击“学习技能”按钮并学习技能“龙破斩”。"
"[english]ag_objective_LinaUnlockAbilityBody"	"Press the \"Level Up\" button and learn the Dragon Slave ability."
"ag_info_AbilityItemBuildLunaTitle"	"技能和出装选择：输出和存活"
"[english]ag_info_AbilityItemBuildLunaTitle"	"Ability & Item Builds: Damage and Survival"
"ag_info_AbilityItemBuildLunaBody"	"这场比赛中英雄的技能加点和出装顺序均为预先设置。\n\n在比赛的进程中，预设的装备会使你的物理攻击在造成伤害的同时恢复自己的生命。也能帮助你在冲向敌人时施放强大的终极技能，毁灭周围的敌人。"
"[english]ag_info_AbilityItemBuildLunaBody"	"For this match you will have preset Ability and Item build orders.\n\nAs you progress, your items will enable you to deal damaging attacks which also heal you as they bounce between targets. This will help you to survive as you charge enemies and launch your powerful ultimate ability, which can destroy nearby foes."
"ag_info_AbilityItemBuildSvenTitle"	"技能和出装选择：肉盾和输出"
"[english]ag_info_AbilityItemBuildSvenTitle"	"Ability & Item Builds: Durability and Damage"
"ag_info_AbilityItemBuildSvenBody"	"这场比赛中英雄的技能加点和出装顺序均为预先设置。\n\n在比赛的进程中，预设的装备会提升你的护甲和攻击力，让你能快速接近敌人，将他们击倒。"
"[english]ag_info_AbilityItemBuildSvenBody"	"For this match you will have preset Ability and Item build orders.\n\nAs you progress, your items will increase your armor and attack damage, allowing you to close the distance to your enemy and then cut them down."
"ag_info_AbilityItemBuildLinaTitle"	"技能和出装选择：撑魔频繁施放技能"
"[english]ag_info_AbilityItemBuildLinaTitle"	"Ability & Item Builds: Mana to Cast Abilities Often"
"ag_info_AbilityItemBuildLinaBody"	"这场比赛中英雄的技能加点和出装顺序均为预先设置。\n\n在比赛的进程中，预设的装备会给予额外的魔法值和魔法恢复速率，使莉娜能频繁地施放她强大又耗魔的技能。"
"[english]ag_info_AbilityItemBuildLinaBody"	"For this match you will have preset Ability and Item build orders.\n\nAs you progress, your items will grant you additional mana and mana regeneration, making it possible to cast Lina's extremely powerful and costly spells more often."
"ag_objective_BuyItemsTitle"	"作战准备"
"[english]ag_objective_BuyItemsTitle"	"Preparing for Combat"
"ag_objective_BuyItemsBody"	"购买初始装备。（打开商店，右键点击图标）"
"[english]ag_objective_BuyItemsBody"	"Buy your starting items. (Open the shop and right-click icons)"
"ag_info_LaningTitle"	"游戏前期：攻击小兵获得金钱并保证存活"
"[english]ag_info_LaningTitle"	"Early Game: Survive While Earning Gold from Creeps"
"ag_info_LaningBody"	"你将与戴泽一同前往下路，他会运用治疗能力辅助你。\n\n你的首要目标就是赚取金钱，同时千万不要阵亡！\n\n一旦死亡就麻烦了；不仅敌人会因为将你击杀而提升力量，而且你的金钱会有不小的损失。"
"[english]ag_info_LaningBody"	"You will be going to the Bottom Lane and partnered with Dazzle, who will support you with his healing powers.\n\nYour top priorities for now are to earn gold and above all, SURVIVE!\n\nDying isn't just inconvenient; enemies will gain power for killing you, and you will lose a portion of your gold."
"ag_objective_MoveToLaneTitle"	"游戏前期：向一条分路移动"
"[english]ag_objective_MoveToLaneTitle"	"Early Game: Move to Your Lane"
"ag_objective_MoveToLaneBody"	"向下路移动（右键点击移动）。"
"[english]ag_objective_MoveToLaneBody"	"Move to the Bottom Lane (right-click to move)."
"ag_info_LaningIntroTitle"	"游戏前期：战斗开始"
"[english]ag_info_LaningIntroTitle"	"Early Game: The Battle Begins"
"ag_info_LaningIntroBody"	"即将有一波小兵产生，跟随他们前去战斗，你的攻击能支援他们。\n\n小兵会自动朝敌方基地行进，遇到敌方单位或建筑就会停下来攻击。\n\n一波小兵全部阵亡后，后撤并与下一波小兵会合。"
"[english]ag_info_LaningIntroBody"	"A wave of creeps is about to spawn. Follow them into battle and support them with your attacks.\n\nCreeps automatically march toward the enemy base, attacking any enemy units or buildings they encounter.\n\nWhen a wave of creeps dies, back up and regroup with the next creep wave."
"ag_objective_GetLastHitsTitle"	"游戏前期：获取金钱"
"[english]ag_objective_GetLastHitsTitle"	"Early Game: Earning Gold"
"ag_objective_GetLastHitsBody"	"对敌人发动最后一击，赚取金钱。"
"[english]ag_objective_GetLastHitsBody"	"Strike Last Hits on enemy creeps to earn gold."
"ag_info_CoreItemsTitle"	"游戏前期：装备购买"
"[english]ag_info_CoreItemsTitle"	"Early Game: Purchase Items"
"ag_info_CoreItemsBody"	"你的补刀越来越熟练了。\n\n继续赚取金钱，购买所有前期装备。\n\n这些装备会加强你的作战能力，为游戏中期做好铺垫。"
"[english]ag_info_CoreItemsBody"	"You're getting better at striking Last Hits.\n\nContinue earning gold and purchase all of your Early Game Items.\n\nThese items will help you become an effective warrior before you begin to move around the battlefield in the Mid Game."
"ag_objective_BuyEarlyItemsTitle"	"游戏前期：装备购买"
"[english]ag_objective_BuyEarlyItemsTitle"	"Early Game: Purchase Items"
"ag_objective_BuyEarlyItemsBody"	"获取金钱并购买前期装备。"
"[english]ag_objective_BuyEarlyItemsBody"	"Earn gold and buy your Early Game Items."
"ag_info_TakeObjectivesTitle"	"游戏中期：摧毁防御塔并向胜利推进"
"[english]ag_info_TakeObjectivesTitle"	"Mid Game: Destroy Towers and Push Toward Victory"
"ag_info_TakeObjectivesBody"	"现在有了前期装备后，可以专注于一个目标，那就是摧毁三条线上所有的防御塔。\n\n金钱和经验的获取依然很重要，不过现在可以在战场上进行游走，摧毁敌方的防御塔。"
"[english]ag_info_TakeObjectivesBody"	"Now that you have your Early Game Items, it's time to focus on objectives, and destroy the Towers in all three lanes.\n\nIt's still important for you to gain gold and experience, but now you should begin moving around the battlefield to join your teammates and destroy enemy Towers."
"ag_objective_TakeTowersTitle"	"游戏前期：摧毁防御塔并消灭英雄"
"[english]ag_objective_TakeTowersTitle"	"Mid Game: Destroy Towers and Heroes"
"ag_objective_TakeTowersBody"	"击杀前来防守的敌方英雄，并摧毁基地外的防御塔。"
"[english]ag_objective_TakeTowersBody"	"Kill defending enemy Heroes and destroy the Towers outside their base."
"ag_info_HighgroundTitle"	"游戏后期：进攻敌方的基地"
"[english]ag_info_HighgroundTitle"	"Late Game: Assaulting the Enemy Base"
"ag_info_HighgroundBody"	"是时候进攻敌方基地了！基地里，每条线上都会有一座防御塔和一对兵营。摧毁兵营会使相应线上的小兵得到强化。\n\n在进攻敌方遗迹前，必须先摧毁守护遗迹的两座防御塔。将敌方遗迹摧毁即可获得比赛的胜利。"
"[english]ag_info_HighgroundBody"	"It's time to attack the enemy base! Inside, you'll find a Tower and pair of Barracks in each lane. Destroying an enemy Barracks will strengthen your creeps in that lane.\n\nTo attack the enemy's Ancient, first destroy the two Towers guarding it. Destroy the enemy's Ancient to win the match."
"ag_objective_DestroyAncientTitle"	"游戏后期：摧毁遗迹"
"[english]ag_objective_DestroyAncientTitle"	"Late Game: Destroy Their Ancient"
"ag_objective_DestroyAncientBody"	"摧毁敌方遗迹，获得比赛的胜利。"
"[english]ag_objective_DestroyAncientBody"	"Destroy the enemy's Ancient to win the match."
"ag_info_FoundARuneTitle"	"神符：两分钟一次的加成效果"
"[english]ag_info_FoundARuneTitle"	"Runes: Various Bonuses Every Two Minutes"
"ag_info_FoundARuneBody"	"你正在靠近一个神符。神符有多种类型，每一种激活后都会使英雄获得显著的加成效果。\n\n每隔两分钟，神符就会在河道的上下两端各出现一个。"
"[english]ag_info_FoundARuneBody"	"You are approaching a Rune. There are several types of Runes, and each provides a significant bonus to your hero when activated.\n\nNew Runes will appear at the north and south ends of the river every two minutes."
"ag_info_RoshanTitle"	"Roshan与不朽之守护"
"[english]ag_info_RoshanTitle"	"Roshan & Aegis of the Immortal"
"ag_info_RoshanBody"	"Roshan是极其强大的中立生物。他被击杀后会掉落不朽之守护。\n\n携带不朽之守护的英雄死亡后会在原地立刻复活。\n\nRoshan被击杀后经过八到十一分钟不等的时间会在他的巢穴重新出现。"
"[english]ag_info_RoshanBody"	"Roshan is an extremely powerful neutral monster. If a team gathers and slays him, he will leave behind the Aegis of the Immortal.\n\nIf a hero holding the Aegis dies, they will immediately revive at the location of their death.\n\nOnce killed, Roshan will reappear in his pit after eight to eleven minutes."
"ag_info_CreepCampsTitle"	"野怪营地：另一个力量源头"
"[english]ag_info_CreepCampsTitle"	"Jungle Creep Camps: Another Source of Power"
"ag_info_CreepCampsBody"	"兵线之间的树林被称为野区。在野区中有几处中立生物所在的营地。\n\n如果英雄足够强大，可以通过击杀这些野怪获得金钱和经验。每隔一分钟，被清空的野怪营地会刷新一组野怪。"
"[english]ag_info_CreepCampsBody"	"The forests between the lanes are called the Jungle. Throughout the Jungle are several camps filled with neutral creep monsters.\n\nIf your hero is powerful enough, these creeps can provide an alternative way to earn gold and experience. Empty creep camps refill every minute."
"ag_info_SideShopTitle"	"边路商店：战场中的供给站"
"[english]ag_info_SideShopTitle"	"The Side Shop: Supplies in the Field"
"ag_info_SideShopBody"	"边路商店在上下路靠近河道的地方各有一处。\n\n商店中出售各类在游戏前期非常有用的装备，包括多种鞋类装备的配件，还有可用于传送至其他地点的回程卷轴。"
"[english]ag_info_SideShopBody"	"Side Shops can be found just outside of the Top and Bottom Lanes near the river.\n\nThey sell various items useful in the Early Game, including the components for several types of boots, as well as Town Portal Scrolls which are used to teleport around the battlefield."
"ag_info_VictoryTitle"	"胜利！"
"[english]ag_info_VictoryTitle"	"Victory!"
"ag_info_VictoryBody"	"恭喜！现在你可以尝试真正的比赛了。\n\n如果想要了解其他英雄，或者继续练习本英雄，点击主界面下“英雄”按钮，查看相应的英雄并使用“试玩英雄”功能。\n\nDota最适合与三两好友一同游戏，组个小队玩的更加开心！"
"[english]ag_info_VictoryBody"	"Congratulations! You are now ready for a real match.\n\nIf you would like to learn about other heroes, or practice more with this one, visit the \"Heroes\" tab and use the \"Demo Hero\" feature.\n\nDota is best enjoyed with friends, so form a party and have fun!"
"ag_alert_TooManyTowerHitsTitle"	"防御塔伤害过高"
"[english]ag_alert_TooManyTowerHitsTitle"	"Excessive Tower Damage"
"ag_alert_TooManyTowerHitsBody"	"防御塔极其致命！\n\n赶紧后撤，让小兵去承受它的攻击。"
"[english]ag_alert_TooManyTowerHitsBody"	"Towers are deadly!\n\nRetreat and let your creeps suffer its attacks instead."
"ag_alert_TooManyCreepHitsTitle"	"小兵伤害过高"
"[english]ag_alert_TooManyCreepHitsTitle"	"Excessive Creep Damage"
"ag_alert_TooManyCreepHitsBody"	"你正在承受大量来自小兵的攻击！\n\n尽管小兵会攻击首先遇到的敌人，如果你攻击敌方的英雄，他们会转而攻击你。"
"[english]ag_alert_TooManyCreepHitsBody"	"You are taking a lot of damage from Creeps!\n\nThough creeps will attack the first enemy they encounter, they will switch to attacking you if you attack a hero on their team."
"ag_alert_CanPurchaseItemsTitle"	"花费金钱"
"[english]ag_alert_CanPurchaseItemsTitle"	"Spend your gold"
"ag_alert_CanPurchaseItemsBody"	"按下{g:dota_key:keyname}键购买快速购买的装备。"
"[english]ag_alert_CanPurchaseItemsBody"	"Press {g:dota_key:keyname} to buy a Quick Buy item."
"ag_alert_LowHealthTitle"	"血量过低"
"[english]ag_alert_LowHealthTitle"	"Low Health"
"ag_alert_LowHealthBody"	"你的血量过低。\n\n赶快使用治疗药膏或树之祭祀进行恢复。"
"[english]ag_alert_LowHealthBody"	"Your health is low.\n\nUse a Healing Salve or a Tango to heal."
"ag_alert_FirstPurchaseTitle"	"对线时购买：随时进行快速购买"
"[english]ag_alert_FirstPurchaseTitle"	"Buying in Lane: Quick Buy at any Time"
"ag_alert_FirstPurchaseBody"	"我们已经把需要的物品放到了屏幕下方的快速购买栏。鼠标移到上面并右键点击或直接按下{g:dota_key:keyname}键就可以完成购买。\n\n当你身在战场时，从基地商店购买的物品会被放入储藏处中。按下{g:dota_key:keyname2}键，己方信使就会把物品从储藏处中取出，并运送给你。"
"[english]ag_alert_FirstPurchaseBody"	"We have placed the items you will need in the Quick Buy tray near the bottom of the screen. Purchase items by right-clicking on them there, or by pressing {g:dota_key:keyname}.\n\nItems purchased from your base's shop while you are in the field are placed in your Stash. You can have your team's Courier deliver items from your Stash by pressing {g:dota_key:keyname2}."
"ag_alert_ForcePurchaseItemsTitle"	"消费金钱！"
"[english]ag_alert_ForcePurchaseItemsTitle"	"Spend your gold!"
"ag_alert_ForcePurchaseItemsBody"	"你有大笔金钱未进行消费。去买点东西吧。别忘了，阵亡的话会损失金钱！"
"[english]ag_alert_ForcePurchaseItemsBody"	"You have a lot of unspent gold. Buy something. Remember, you lose gold when you die!"
"ag_alert_NeedDeliverItemsTitle"	"储藏处内物品"
"[english]ag_alert_NeedDeliverItemsTitle"	"Items in Your Stash"
"ag_alert_NeedDeliverItemsBody"	"按下{g:dota_key:keyname}键后己方信使就会取出储藏处内物品并运送给你。"
"[english]ag_alert_NeedDeliverItemsBody"	"Press {g:dota_key:keyname} to have the items in your Stash delivered by your team's courier."
"ag_alert_CanLevelUpTitle"	"升级"
"[english]ag_alert_CanLevelUpTitle"	"Level Up"
"ag_alert_CanLevelUpBody"	"学习新的技能，或加强已有技能。"
"[english]ag_alert_CanLevelUpBody"	"Learn a new ability, or strengthen an existing one."
"ag_alert_ForceLevelUpTitle"	"升级！"
"[english]ag_alert_ForceLevelUpTitle"	"Level Up!"
"ag_alert_ForceLevelUpBody"	"你的技能点还未用完。可以将其用在一个技能上。"
"[english]ag_alert_ForceLevelUpBody"	"You haven't used all of your Level Points. Add points to a skill."
"ag_alert_BehindOnTowersTitle"	"摧毁防御塔"
"[english]ag_alert_BehindOnTowersTitle"	"Destroy Towers"
"ag_alert_BehindOnTowersBody"	"在敌人摧毁我方防御塔前先摧毁他们的！"
"[english]ag_alert_BehindOnTowersBody"	"Destroy enemy Towers before the enemy can destroy yours!"
"ag_alert_BehindOnGoldTitle"	"金钱落后"
"[english]ag_alert_BehindOnGoldTitle"	"Behind on Gold"
"ag_alert_BehindOnGoldBody"	"补到更多的小兵，不能让金钱落后太多。"
"[english]ag_alert_BehindOnGoldBody"	"Last Hit more creeps to catch up on gold."
"ag_alert_BehindOnExpTitle"	"经验落后"
"[english]ag_alert_BehindOnExpTitle"	"Behind on Experience"
"ag_alert_BehindOnExpBody"	"想要获得经验可不能离战场太远。"
"[english]ag_alert_BehindOnExpBody"	"Stay near combat to earn experience."
"ag_alert_UseSalveTitle"	"你受伤了"
"[english]ag_alert_UseSalveTitle"	"You Are Hurt"
"ag_alert_UseSalveBody"	"使用治疗药膏来进行治疗。一旦受到伤害，治疗效果就会中断。"
"[english]ag_alert_UseSalveBody"	"Use a Healing Salve to heal. Taking damage cancels the effect."
"ag_alert_UseClarityTitle"	"回复魔法"
"[english]ag_alert_UseClarityTitle"	"Restore Mana"
"ag_alert_UseClarityBody"	"使用净化药水来恢复魔法。期间受到伤害将中断恢复效果。"
"[english]ag_alert_UseClarityBody"	"Use a Clarity to restore mana. Taking damage cancels the effect."
"ag_alert_RespawnTitle"	"复活"
"[english]ag_alert_RespawnTitle"	"Respawn"
"ag_alert_RespawnBody"	"英雄即将复活。\n\n可以试试快速回到战斗！"
"[english]ag_alert_RespawnBody"	"Your hero will respawn soon.\n\nTry to get back into the action quickly!"
"ag_alert_TangoUsageTitle"	"树之祭祀"
"[english]ag_alert_TangoUsageTitle"	"Tangos"
"ag_alert_TangoUsageBody"	"树之祭祀可以使你消耗树木来持续回复少量生命。\n\n现在左键点击树木就可以使用树之祭祀。"
"[english]ag_alert_TangoUsageBody"	"Tangos let you eat a tree to heal your hero over time.\n\nLeft-click on a tree to use a tango."
"ag_alert_SalveUsageTitle"	"治疗药膏"
"[english]ag_alert_SalveUsageTitle"	"Healing Salve"
"ag_alert_SalveUsageBody"	"治疗药膏可以快速恢复目标英雄的生命（左键点击使用。）\n\n一旦受到伤害，治疗效果就会中断。"
"[english]ag_alert_SalveUsageBody"	"Healing Salves can quickly heal the hero you target (left-click).\n\nTaking damage will cancel the effect."
"ag_alert_ClarityUsageTitle"	"净化药水"
"[english]ag_alert_ClarityUsageTitle"	"Clarity"
"ag_alert_ClarityUsageBody"	"净化药水可以使目标英雄缓慢恢复魔法。\n\n一旦受到伤害，恢复效果就会中断。"
"[english]ag_alert_ClarityUsageBody"	"Clarity slowly regenerates the mana of the hero you target (left click).\n\nTaking damage will cancel the effect."
"ag_ExcessiveTowerDamageTitle"	"防御塔非常危险。赶快后撤！"
"[english]ag_ExcessiveTowerDamageTitle"	"Towers are Dangerous. Retreat!"
"ag_ExcessiveTowerDamageBody"	"哎呦！防御塔正对你造成成吨的伤害！\n\n赶快后撤，让防御塔攻击其他目标。"
"[english]ag_ExcessiveTowerDamageBody"	"Ouch! You are taking a lot of damage from the Tower!\n\nBack up until the Tower begins to attack something else."
"ag_alert_DeathTitle"	"死亡与复活"
"[english]ag_alert_DeathTitle"	"Death & Respawning"
"ag_alert_DeathBody"	"死亡后将会损失部分金钱，而且击杀你的英雄将获得经验。\n\n在死亡时间结束后英雄将会在己方的泉水复活。复活倒计时会在屏幕顶部的英雄肖像下方显示。\n\n每提升一级，复活时间也会相应地有所增加。"
"[english]ag_alert_DeathBody"	"When you die, you lose a portion of your gold, and the hero or heroes responsible for your death earn experience to become stronger.\n\nYou will respawn at your team's fountain when your death timer ends. You can see your death timer beneath your hero's portrait at the top of the screen.\n\nEach level gained increases how long a hero remains dead."
"ag_alert_FountainTitle"	"泉水：疗伤源泉"
"[english]ag_alert_FountainTitle"	"The Fountain: A Source of Healing"
"ag_alert_FountainBody"	"如果在战斗中阵亡，英雄会在此处复活。返回泉水可以快速恢复生命和魔法。"
"[english]ag_alert_FountainBody"	"After death, your hero will respawn at their team's fountain. Returning to the Fountain will quickly restore your health and mana."
"ag_alert_ScrollTitle"	"回程卷轴：在战场上传送"
"[english]ag_alert_ScrollTitle"	"Town Portal Scrolls: Teleport Around the Battlefield"
"ag_alert_ScrollBody"	"在战场上快速移动非常重要。\n\n回程卷轴在商店有售，可以使你传送至己方的防御塔或其他建筑物。\n\n使用卷轴时，先左键点击卷轴，再左键点击小地图上的己方建筑就会开始传送。"
"[english]ag_alert_ScrollBody"	"Moving around the battlefield quickly is important.\n\nTown Portal Scrolls can be purchased from the shop, and allow you to teleport to an allied Tower or other building.\n\nTo use a Scroll, left-click on the item, then left-click on an allied building on the minimap to teleport there."
"ag_alert_ScrollUsageTitle"	"回程卷轴"
"[english]ag_alert_ScrollUsageTitle"	"Town Portal Scroll"
"ag_alert_ScrollUsageBody"	"购买并使用回程卷轴。使用卷轴时，先左键点击卷轴，再左键点击小地图上的己方建筑就会开始传送。"
"[english]ag_alert_ScrollUsageBody"	"Purchase and use a Town Portal Scroll. To use the Scroll, left-click on the item, then left-click on any allied building on the minimap to teleport there."
"ag_alert_SecretShopTitle"	"神秘商店：出售独家物品"
"[english]ag_alert_SecretShopTitle"	"Secret Shop: Items not available elsewhere"
"ag_alert_SecretShopBody"	"部分物品只能在神秘商店购买。如果在神秘商店范围外尝试购买这些物品，小地图上会出现相应标记提示你前去购买。"
"[english]ag_alert_SecretShopBody"	"Some items can only be purchased from a Secret Shop. If you try to buy one of these items while out of range of a Secret Shop, a marker will appear to tell you where to go."
"ag_alert_SecretShopFoundTitle"	"神秘商店：其实并不神秘"
"[english]ag_alert_SecretShopFoundTitle"	"The Secret Shop: Not Actually a Secret"
"ag_alert_SecretShopFoundBody"	"欢迎光临神秘商店。\n\n河道两侧各有一个神秘商店，而且出售的物品相同。你前往对面的神秘商店同样可以购买物品。"
"[english]ag_alert_SecretShopFoundBody"	"Welcome to the Secret Shop.\n\nThere is a Secret Shop on both sides of the river, and both sell the same items. Either team can use either Secret Shop."
"ag_detail_BaseStatsTitle"	"技能：属性点 - 提升英雄全属性"
"[english]ag_detail_BaseStatsTitle"	"Ability: Attributes - Increase Your Primary Stats"
"ag_detail_BaseStatsBody"	"技能点也可以用于使自己的三项属性永久增加。每项属性的效果各有不同：\n- 敏捷提升护甲和攻击速度，还能提升如露娜等敏捷型英雄的攻击力。\n-智力提升最大魔法值和魔法恢复速率，还能提升如莉娜等智力型英雄的攻击力。"
"[english]ag_detail_BaseStatsBody"	"Level Points can also be spent to permanently increase all three of your attributes. Each attribute does something different:\n\n- Strength increases health, and adds attack damage for Strength heroes such as Sven.\n- Agility increases armor and attack speed, and adds attack damage for Agility heroes such as Luna.\n- Intelligence increases maximum mana and mana regeneration, and adds attack damage for Intelligence heroes such as Lina."
"ag_detail_InventoryTitle"	"管理物品栏"
"[english]ag_detail_InventoryTitle"	"Managing Your Inventory"
"ag_detail_InventoryBody"	"你也许发现物品栏没有格子放新物品。清出格子的最佳方法是利用现有物品合成更加强大的物品。\n\n如果现有物品都无法进行合成，那可以将其出售，在任意商店附近右键点击想要出售的物品，选择“出售”。"
"[english]ag_detail_InventoryBody"	"You may find yourself without inventory space for new items. The best way to clear space is to buy items which can be combined to create other, more powerful items.\n\nIf none of your items can be combined, you can sell an item by visiting any shop, right-clicking on what you wish to sell, and selecting \"Sell\"."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaTreadsTitle"	"装备详情：动力鞋 - 加快移速并强化攻击"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaTreadsTitle"	"Item Details: Power Treads - Faster Movement and Stronger Attacks"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaTreadsBody"	"鞋类物品是游戏中最重要的物品之一。移动速度在追击、逃跑时都非常关键。\n\n动力鞋可以提升攻击速度，使露娜更好地发挥出高攻击力的优势，而且还可以点击，切换加成的属性。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaTreadsBody"	"Boots are one of the most important items in the game. Movement speed is crucial for chasing down, or retreating from, an opponent.\n\nPower Treads complement Luna's high attack damage with increased attack speed, and can be activated to switch the primary attribute they increase."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaAquilaTitle"	"装备详情：天鹰之戒 - （低）敏捷和攻击力加成"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaAquilaTitle"	"Item Details: Ring of Aquila - Added Agility, Increased Damage, and More"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaAquilaBody"	"露娜的主属性是敏捷，而怨灵系带提供了可观的敏捷加成。\n\n将怨灵系带升级成天鹰之戒可以使露娜在不必花很多金钱的情况下提升攻击力，魔法恢复速率和护甲，这件物品对露娜而言是非常优秀的前期装备。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaAquilaBody"	"Luna's primary attribute is Agility, and Wraith Band provides an affordable boost to Agility.\n\nUpgrading a Wraith Band into a Ring of Aquila is an economical way to add attack damage, mana regeneration, and armor, making this an excellent item for Luna."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaLifestealTitle"	"装备详情：死亡面具 - 低吸血效果"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaLifestealTitle"	"Item Details: Morbid Mask - Healing with Each Attack"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaLifestealBody"	"保持较高的血量非常重要。吸血面具可以使你在攻击时按造成的伤害被动地回复生命值。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaLifestealBody"	"Keeping your health up is very important. Morbid Mask passively heals you for a portion of the damage you deal with attacks."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaYashaTitle"	"装备详情：夜叉 - 增加移速和敏捷"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaYashaTitle"	"Item Details: Yasha - Added Speed and Agility"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaYashaBody"	"夜叉为攻击效果和移动速度提供了可观的加成，并增加了不少敏捷，提升了露娜的攻击力。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaYashaBody"	"Yasha provides a considerable boost to attack and movement speed, and a lot of Agility, which increases Luna's attack damage."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaHelmTitle"	"装备详情：支配头盔 - 增加伤害并控制野怪"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaHelmTitle"	"Item Details: Helm of the Dominator - Added Damage and Controlling Creeps"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaHelmBody"	"吸血面具升级后可以提供额外的攻击力和护甲。\n\n而且，使用头盔可以将敌方小兵作为目标进行支配，取得对小兵的控制。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaHelmBody"	"This upgrade to the Morbid Mask provides additional damage and armor.\n\nAlso, activating the Helm allows you to Dominate a target enemy creep, granting you full control of that creep."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaMantaTitle"	"装备详情：幻影斧 - 大幅提升属性并拥有幻象技能"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaMantaTitle"	"Item Details: Manta Style - Major Boosts and Illusions"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaMantaBody"	"幻影斧提供的属性加成比夜叉更高。\n\n使用幻影斧可以创造两个英雄的幻象，也就是复制体。你可以控制幻象攻击敌人。幻象往往会比原英雄弱。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaMantaBody"	"Manta Style grants larger bonuses than Yasha provides.\n\nActivating Manta Style creates two illusions, or copies, of your hero. These can be ordered to attack enemies. Illusions from any source are weaker than their source hero."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaBKBTitle"	"装备详情：黑皇杖 - 对大部分技能免疫"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaBKBTitle"	"Item Details: Black King Bar - Immunity from Spells"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaBKBBody"	"黑黄杖在使用后，英雄就会完全地免疫绝大多数敌人技能的效果和伤害。不过每使用一次，免疫效果的持续时间都会有所减少。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaBKBBody"	"When Black King Bar is activated, your hero becomes completely immune to the effects and damage from most enemy abilities. However, with each activation, the duration of this immunity is decreased."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaButterflyTitle"	"装备详情：蝴蝶 - 大量加成效果和非常有用的闪避"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaButterflyTitle"	"Item Details: Butterfly - Massive Boosts and Helpful Evasion"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaButterflyBody"	"蝴蝶可以大幅提升攻击力，攻击速度和敏捷，以及会导致敌人攻击丢失的闪避效果。\n\n主动技能振翅牺牲了闪避效果，获得移动速度的爆发。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaButterflyBody"	"Butterfly provides a huge bonus to damage, attack speed, and Agility, while the evasion it provides makes you harder to hit.\n\nIts activation ability, Flutter, trades away its evasion for a quick burst of additional movement speed."
"ag_detail_ItemLunaSatanicTitle"	"装备详情：撒旦之协力 - 高吸血效果"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaSatanicTitle"	"Item Details: Satanic - Increased Healing with Each Attack"
"ag_detail_ItemLunaSatanicBody"	"撒旦之邪力提供非常多的力量，可以显著地提高露娜的生命值。\n\n启动撒旦之邪力可以暂时提高吸血效果，在战斗中快速恢复生命值。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLunaSatanicBody"	"Satanic grants a large amount of Strength, which for Luna means more health.\n\nActivating Satanic temporarily increases its lifesteal to be higher than the damage you deal, making it a great way to refill your health during a fight."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenTreadsTitle"	"装备详情：动力鞋 - 加快移速并强化攻击"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenTreadsTitle"	"Item Details: Power Treads - Faster Movement and Stronger Attacks"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenTreadsBody"	"鞋类物品是游戏中最重要的物品之一。移动速度在追击、逃跑时都非常关键。\n\n动力鞋可以提升攻击速度，使斯温更好地发挥出高攻击力的优势，而且还可以点击，切换加成的属性。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenTreadsBody"	"Boots are one of the most important items in the game. Movement speed is crucial for chasing down, or retreating from, an opponent.\n\nPower Treads compliment Sven's high attack damage with increased attack speed, and can be activated to switch the primary attribute they increase."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenDrumsTitle"	"装备详情：韧鼓 - 多种加成效果"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenDrumsTitle"	"Item Details: Drum of Endurance - Helpful Boosts"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenDrumsBody"	"韧鼓可以让斯温的力量，敏捷和智力均得到提升，同时斯温和附近友方英雄的攻击速度和移动速度都获得了加成。这对团战的帮助尤其突出。\n\n激活韧鼓还可以短暂地提高攻速和移速的加成效果。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenDrumsBody"	"Drum of Endurance provides an increase to Sven's strength, agility, and intelligence, while also boosting the attack and movement speed of Sven and nearby allied heroes. This makes it especially useful in a team fight.\n\nActivating the Drum will temporarily increase the speed bonuses."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenLifestealTitle"	"装备详情：死亡面具 - 低吸血效果"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenLifestealTitle"	"Item Details: Morbid Mask - Healing With Each Attack"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenLifestealBody"	"保持较高的血量非常重要。吸血面具可以使你在攻击时按造成的伤害被动地回复生命值，时刻保证自己血量。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenLifestealBody"	"Keeping your health up is very important. The Morbid Mask passively heals you for a portion of the damage you deal with attacks, making it easier to keep your health up."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenCritTitle"	"装备详情：水晶剑 - 攻击力提升与致命一击"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenCritTitle"	"Item Details: Crystalys - Added Damage & Critical Strikes"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenCritBody"	"水晶剑能够提供大量攻击力加成。而且每次攻击都有几率造成致命一击，使伤害更高。时机正好的致命一击，配合斯温的巨力挥舞技能，可以迅速扭转战局。\n\n通常情况下，水晶剑是合成代达罗斯之殇的过渡装备。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenCritBody"	"Crystalys provides a large boost to attack damage. It also gives each attack a chance to become a critical strike, which deals double damage. A lucky critical strike, combined with Sven's Great Cleave ability, can quickly turn the tide of battle.\n\nGenerally, Crystalys is purchased in order to build the more powerful Daedalus."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenMaskTitle"	"装备详情：疯狂面具 - 有代价的攻击爆发"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenMaskTitle"	"Item Details: Mask of Madness - Attack Damage at a Cost"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenMaskBody"	"疯狂面具小幅提升了吸血面具的吸血效果，而且拥有非常强大的主动技能：狂热。\n\n激活后，狂热会加强一定时间内的攻击输出，攻击速度和移动速度均有大幅提升。但是，狂热会让你承受额外伤害。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenMaskBody"	"Providing a small increase to Morbid Mask's ability to heal with each attack, Mask of Madness has a powerful activation ability: Berserk.\n\nWhen activated, Berserk significantly increases how quickly you attack and move. However, while active Berserk also causes you to take additional damage."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenPlatemailTitle"	"装备详情：板甲 - 抵抗物理攻击"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenPlatemailTitle"	"Item Details: Platemail - Resistance to Attacks"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenPlatemailBody"	"每提升1点护甲，被敌人攻击时受到的伤害就能减少约6%。板甲提供的护甲将被动地增加到斯温本身的护甲中，而且加上能够增加护甲的战吼技能，他可以在敌人的攻击下屹立不倒。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenPlatemailBody"	"Each point of armor decreases how much damage a hero takes from enemy attacks by 6%. The armor from Platemail is passively added with Sven's innate armor and, if combined with his armor-granting Warcry ability, can make him extremely difficult to take down."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenHyperstoneTitle"	"装备详情：振奋宝石 - 大幅提升攻击速度"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenHyperstoneTitle"	"Item Details: Hyperstone - Attack Speed Boost"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenHyperstoneBody"	"振奋宝石可以大幅提升英雄的攻击速度。\n\n对于本身攻击力不低的英雄来说，提升攻击速度可以达到较好的伤害输出效果。振奋宝石也是合成几个强大物品的配件之一。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenHyperstoneBody"	"Hyperstone provides a major increase to a hero's attack speed.\n\nIncreasing the attack speed of a hero whose attacks already deal a lot of damage is a great way to destroy enemies. Hyperstone is also a component of several other powerful items."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenAssaultTitle"	"装备详情：强袭胸甲 - 攻击速度和护甲光环"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenAssaultTitle"	"Item Details: Assault Cuirass - Attack speed and Armor aura"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenAssaultBody"	"强袭胸甲大幅提升了攻击速度和护甲。\n\n而且可以提升附近友方单位的护甲和攻击速度，同时减少附近敌方单位的护甲，是战场上效果非常突出的装备。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenAssaultBody"	"Assault Cuirass provides a significant boost to attack speed, and a lot of armor.\n\nIt also passively increases the armor and attack speed of nearby allies, while reducing the armor of nearby enemies, making it an excellent item to bring into battle."
"ag_detail_ItemSvenGreaterCritTitle"	"装备详情：代达罗斯之殇 - 更高攻击力与致命一击伤害"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenGreaterCritTitle"	"Item Details: Daedalus - More Damage & Bigger Critical Strikes"
"ag_detail_ItemSvenGreaterCritBody"	"代达罗斯之殇直接让水晶剑的每个效果都更上一层楼：大幅提升攻击力，并且致命一击的伤害倍率比水晶剑更高。\n\n只要运气不差，配合斯温的巨力挥舞技能，一场团战可能只要一刀就结束了。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemSvenGreaterCritBody"	"Daedalus directly improves on Crystalys in every way: it provides a much larger boost to attack damage, while also giving each attack a chance to become a far stronger critical strike than Crystalys allows.\n\nWith a bit of luck, and Sven's Great Cleave ability, it is possible to end a team fight with a single attack."
"ag_detail_ItemLinaPhaseTitle"	"装备详情：相位鞋 - 可观的攻击力加成"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaPhaseTitle"	"Item Details: Phase Boots - Affordable Attack Damage"
"ag_detail_ItemLinaPhaseBody"	"额外的移动速度加成在撤退或追击敌人时非常关键。\n\n相位鞋还提供可观的攻击力加成，使莉娜更轻松地完成补刀。另外，激活相位鞋后可以直接穿过小兵和英雄。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaPhaseBody"	"The additional movement speed provided by boots is crucial for retreating from, or chasing down, an enemy.\n\nPhase Boots also provide a considerable boost to attack damage, making it easier for Lina to strike last hits. Additionally, activating Phase Boots allows you to walk through creeps and heroes."
"ag_detail_ItemLinaDrumsTitle"	"装备详情：韧鼓 - 多种加成效果"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaDrumsTitle"	"Item Details: Drum of Endurance - Helpful Boosts"
"ag_detail_ItemLinaDrumsBody"	"韧鼓可以让莉娜的力量，敏捷和智力均得到提升，使莉娜在战场中不容易阵亡，同时莉娜和附近友方英雄的攻击速度和移动速度都获得了加成。\n\n激活韧鼓还可以短暂地提高攻速和移速的加成效果。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaDrumsBody"	"Drum of Endurance provides an increase to strength, agility, and intelligence, helping Lina to stay alive in battle while providing her with additional attack damage. It also increases the attack and move speed of Lina and nearby allied heroes.\n\nActivating the Drum will temporarily increase the speed bonuses."
"ag_detail_ItemLinaCycloneTitle"	"装备详情：Eul的神圣法杖 - 机动性和多面性"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaCycloneTitle"	"Item Details: Eul's Scepter of Divinity - Mobility and Versatility"
"ag_detail_ItemLinaCycloneBody"	"神圣法杖提供不低的智力和魔法恢复速率加成，使莉娜可以更加频繁地施放技能。移动速度方面的加成搭配相位鞋和她的被动技能炽魂能获得非常理想的效果。\n\n它的龙卷风技能可以远远地将敌人困在半空中。算好时间，在他落地的时候用光击阵晕住他！"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaCycloneBody"	"Scepter of Divinity provides intelligence and mana regeneration, allowing Lina to cast her abilities more often. Its increases to movement speed also pair well with Phase Boots and her Fiery Soul passive ability.\n\nIts Cyclone ability briefly traps a distant enemy in the air. Try to time a Light Strike Array to explode as they land!"
"ag_detail_ItemLinaSoulBoosterTitle"	"装备详情：振魂石 - 增加生命值和魔法值"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaSoulBoosterTitle"	"Item Details: Soul Booster - Added Health & Mana"
"ag_detail_ItemLinaSoulBoosterBody"	"振魂石提供大量的生命值加成，以及生命恢复速率，对于像莉娜这样脆弱的英雄极其有用。而且还拥有魔法值和魔法恢复速率加成，使莉娜可以更频繁地施放技能。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaSoulBoosterBody"	"Soul Booster provides a lot of additional health, plus health regeneration, which is extremely useful for a fragile hero like Lina. It also adds mana and mana regeneration, allowing Lina to cast her spells more often."
"ag_detail_ItemLinaOctarineTitle"	"装备详情：玲珑心 - 施法者的最爱"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaOctarineTitle"	"Item Details: Octarine Core - Improved Casting"
"ag_detail_ItemLinaOctarineBody"	"玲珑心提升了振魂石的加成效果，包括生命值，魔法值和恢复速率。而且还提供可观的智力加成，使莉娜的魔法值得到提升的同时，攻击力也有所提高。\n\n此外，它可以被动地使施法者按技能造成的伤害回复一定百分比的生命，同时所有冷却时间都有所减少。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaOctarineBody"	"Octarine Core improves on Soul Booster in every way, providing more health, mana, and regeneration. It also provides a major boost to intelligence, further increasing Lina's mana while adding attack damage.\n\nAdditionally, it passively heals the caster for a portion of any damage dealt by abilities, and reduces all cooldown timers."
"ag_detail_ItemLinaMKBTitle"	"装备详情：金箍棒 - 大幅提升攻击力"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaMKBTitle"	"Item Details: Monkey King Bar - Increased Damage"
"ag_detail_ItemLinaMKBBody"	"金箍棒使攻击力得到可观的加成，而且拥有两个额外的效果：每次攻击都有几率造成额外伤害和短暂眩晕的猛击，和确保每次攻击不会被闪避的克敌机先。"
"[english]ag_detail_ItemLinaMKBBody"	"Monkey King Bar grants a major boost to damage, plus two additional benefits: Bash, which causes each attack to have a chance to deal bonus damage along with an interrupting mini-stun, and True Strike, which ensures that every attack against an enemy hero or creep will hit its target."
"ag_detail_BuildLunarBlessingTitle"	"技能：月之祝福 - 攻击力加成与夜间视野"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildLunarBlessingTitle"	"Ability: Lunar Blessing - Attack Booster and Night Vision"
"ag_detail_BuildLunarBlessingBody"	"月之祝福被动地提升露娜和附近所有友方英雄的攻击力。\n\n此技能使露娜更轻松地完成补刀，而且她的队友在攻击敌人和建筑时造成的伤害更高。另外还可以使露娜在夜晚的视野更大。"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildLunarBlessingBody"	"Lunar Blessing passively increases the attack damage of Luna and all nearby allied heroes.\n\nThis ability makes it easier for Luna to strike Last Hits on creeps, and empowers her allies to destroy enemies and their structures. It also allows Luna to see further at night."
"ag_detail_BuildLucentBeamTitle"	"技能：月光 - 远距离快速伤害"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildLucentBeamTitle"	"Ability: Lucent Beam - Swift Damage at Long Range"
"ag_detail_BuildLucentBeamBody"	"月光的施法距离远，冷却时间短，还能短暂地眩晕目标。\n\n低级时伤害较低。但是随着等级的提升会变得很致命。\n\n出于节省魔法的考虑，将技能升到2级后再对敌人使用，骚扰他们并强迫他们后撤。"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildLucentBeamBody"	"Lucent Beam has long range, a short cooldown and stuns its target for a very short period.\n\nAt first, its damage is low. However, it quickly becomes deadly as levels are added.\n\nTo conserve mana, wait until you have level 2 of this ability, and then use it to harass an enemy hero and force them to retreat."
"ag_detail_BuildEclipseTitle"	"技能：月蚀 - 对周围敌人造成大量伤害"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildEclipseTitle"	"Ability: Eclipse - Massive Damage to Nearby Enemies"
"ag_detail_BuildEclipseBody"	"露娜的终极技能，月蚀可以自动施放几道月光，攻击附近的目标。\n\n尽管这是游戏中几个伤害最高的技能之一，但是月光会随机选取目标。所以尽量挑选没有敌方小兵的地点施放，确保所有月光都打击到敌方英雄。"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildEclipseBody"	"Luna's Ultimate ability, Eclipse, automatically casts several of your Lucent Beam attacks at nearby targets.\n\nThough it can be one of the most damaging spells in the game, the beams target random units. Try to cast it when no enemy creeps are nearby, ensuring that all beams strike enemy heroes."
"ag_detail_BuildMoonGlaiveTitle"	"技能：月刃 - 弹射攻击"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildMoonGlaiveTitle"	"Ability: Moon Glaive - Bouncing Attacks"
"ag_detail_BuildMoonGlaiveBody"	"月刃技能被动地使露娜的普通攻击可以在附近的敌人单位之间弹跳。\n\n在战斗中，或者摧毁敌方防御塔时这些弹跳造成的额外伤害相当可观。"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildMoonGlaiveBody"	"The Moon Glaive ability passively causes Luna's regular attacks to bounce between nearby enemy units.\n\nIn a fight, or when destroying enemy Towers, the extra damage provided by these bounces can help significantly."
"ag_detail_BuildStormHammerTitle"	"技能：风暴之拳 - 眩晕成群的敌人"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildStormHammerTitle"	"Ability: Storm Hammer - Stun Groups of Enemies"
"ag_detail_BuildStormHammerBody"	"风暴之拳可以对成群的敌人造成眩晕和伤害，在发起团战或者阻止敌人撤退时效果非常好。可以尝试对远离己方防御塔或者靠近我方防御塔的敌人使用。\n\n斯温拥有的魔法并不多，所以这个技能尽量只对敌方英雄使用。"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildStormHammerBody"	"Storm Hammer stuns and damages a group of enemies and is useful for initiating an assault, or stopping an enemy's retreat. Try to use it on enemies that are far from their Towers, or near one of yours.\n\nSven does not have much mana, so you should only use this ability to hit enemy heroes."
"ag_detail_BuildWarCryTitle"	"技能：战吼 - 速度和护甲暴增"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildWarCryTitle"	"Ability: Warcry - Bursts of Speed and Armor"
"ag_detail_BuildWarCryBody"	"战吼可以大幅提升斯温和附近友方单位的移动速度和护甲，在激烈的团战中非常有用。\n\n达到满级后战吼提供的护甲加成可以使斯温和他的队友非常耐抗敌人的攻击。"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildWarCryBody"	"Warcry boosts the movement speed and armor of Sven and all nearby allied units, and is great for surviving in the thick of battle.\n\nAt maximum level, the armor provided by Warcry makes Sven and his allies extremely resistant to enemy attacks."
"ag_detail_BuildGreatCleaveTitle"	"技能：巨力挥舞 - 攻击可以伤害多个目标"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildGreatCleaveTitle"	"Ability: Great Cleave - Attacks Hit Several Targets"
"ag_detail_BuildGreatCleaveBody"	"巨力挥舞被动地使斯温的攻击可以伤害他面前的所有单位，使他能快速地消灭一波敌方小兵。\n\n过早学习这个技能会将兵线推到敌方防御塔下，使自己处于非常危险的境地。"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildGreatCleaveBody"	"Great Cleave passively causes Sven's attacks to strike all enemies in front of him, making it easy to quickly clear entire waves of enemy creeps, or punish gathered enemy heroes.\n\nLearning this skill too early can cause you to push your creeps into the range of an enemy Tower, which can put you in a dangerous position."
"ag_detail_BuildGodsStrengthTitle"	"技能：神之力量 - 惊人的攻击力"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildGodsStrengthTitle"	"Ability: God's Strength - Incredible Attack Damage"
"ag_detail_BuildGodsStrengthBody"	"斯温的终极技能，神之力量可以极大地提升他的攻击力，使他化身为输出恐怖的战士。\n\n在进入战斗前，或者想要快速摧毁敌方建筑时使用这个技能。"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildGodsStrengthBody"	"Sven's Ultimate ability, God's Strength, drastically increases his attack damage, turning him into a terrifying fighter.\n\nUse this ability when you are about to enter a battle, or if you need to destroy an enemy structure quickly."
"ag_detail_BuildDragonSlaveTitle"	"技能：龙破斩 - 发动火焰波"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildDragonSlaveTitle"	"Ability: Dragon Slave - Launch Waves of Flame"
"ag_detail_BuildDragonSlaveBody"	"龙破斩可以伤害莉娜面前一条线上的所有敌人。技能的冷却时间很短，对成群的敌人快速造成很高的伤害。\n\n在比赛前期，尽量保证在伤害到小兵的同时也伤害到敌方英雄，这样不仅可以完成补刀也能消耗敌人的血量。"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildDragonSlaveBody"	"Dragon Slave burns all enemies in a long, wide line in front Lina. It has a short cooldown and deals enough damage to quickly slay groups of enemies.\n\nEarly in the match, try to hit both creeps and enemy heroes with a single cast, which will help you to earn last hits and scare off enemy heroes."
"ag_detail_BuildLightStrikeTitle"	"技能：光击阵 - 延迟眩晕"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildLightStrikeTitle"	"Ability: Light Strike Array - Delayed Stun"
"ag_detail_BuildLightStrikeBody"	"经过短暂的延迟后，光击阵产生效果，一片区域内所有敌人都将受到伤害并眩晕。\n\n将本技能和龙破斩都升到满级后，可以在光击阵后马上接龙破斩可以快速消灭一波小兵，或者对敌方英雄造成大量伤害。"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildLightStrikeBody"	"After a short delay, Light Strike Array explodes, damaging and stunning all enemies in an area.\n\nOnce you have increased the level of both this and Dragon Slave, try casting Light Strike Array followed by Dragon Slave to quickly destroy a wave of creeps, or deal significant damage to an enemy hero."
"ag_detail_BuildFireySoulTitle"	"技能：炽魂 - 加快移动和攻击速度"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildFireySoulTitle"	"Ability: Fiery Soul - Faster Movement and Attacks"
"ag_detail_BuildFireySoulBody"	"炽魂可以在莉娜施放任意技能后短暂提升她的移动和攻击速度。\n\n在开战时，先施放光击阵和龙破斩的连招可以大幅提升攻击速度。"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildFireySoulBody"	"Fiery Soul causes Lina's movement and attack speed to increase for a short period whenever she casts one of her spells.\n\nAt the start of a battle, try to begin with a Light Strike Array and Dragon Slave combo to boost your attack speed."
"ag_detail_BuildLagunaBladeTitle"	"技能：神灭斩 - 对单体造成大量伤害"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildLagunaBladeTitle"	"Ability: Laguna Blade - Massive Damage to a Target"
"ag_detail_BuildLagunaBladeBody"	"莉娜的终极技能，神灭斩可以对单个目标造成大量伤害。可以寻找已经残血的英雄，用这个技能直接送他上路。"
"[english]ag_detail_BuildLagunaBladeBody"	"Lina's Ultimate ability, Laguna Blade, deals massive damage to a single target. Look for enemy heroes that have taken damage, then blast them with this ability for the kill."
}
